Guide to the Farm Bureau scrapbooks, New York State,1912-1934.
Farm Bureau scrapbooks, New York State,1912-1934.
- Series IX. 1925
  - Tompkins County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Ulster County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Ulster-Sullivan County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Warren County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Washington County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Wayne County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Westchester County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Wyoming County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Yates County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Yates County, 1925 and 1926 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Series X. 1926
  - Albany County, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Allegany County, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Broome County, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Cayuga County, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Chautaugua County, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Chemung County, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Chenango County, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Clinton County, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Columbia County, 1926-1927 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Columbia County, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Cortland County, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Delaware County, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Dutchess County, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Erie County, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Essex County, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Franklin County, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Fulton County, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Genesee County, 1926 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Greene County, 1926 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Herkimer County, 1926 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Jefferson County, 1925, 1926 and 1929 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Lewis County, 1926 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Livingston County, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Madison County, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Monroe County, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Montgomery County, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Nassau County, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Niagara County, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Oneida County, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Onondaga County, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Ontario County, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Oswego County, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Otsego County, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Rensselaer County, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Rockland County, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Saratoga County, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Schenectady County, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Schoharie County, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Schuyler County, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Seneca County, 1926 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Seneca County, 1926 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - St. Lawrence County, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Steuben County, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Suffolk County, 1926 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Suffolk County, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Sullivan County, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Sullivan-Ulster County, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Ulster County (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Tioga County, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Tompkins County, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Ulster-Sullivan County, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Warren County, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Washington County, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Wayne County, 1926 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Westchester County, 1926 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Wyoming County, 1926 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Yates County, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Yates County, 1925 and 1926 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Series XI. 1927
  - Agricultural County, 1925 and 1927 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Albany County, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Allegany County, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Allegany County, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Allegany County, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Broome County, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Broome County, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Cattaraugus County, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Cayuga County, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Chautaugua County, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Chemung County, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Chenango County, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Clinton County, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Columbia County, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Cortland County, 1927-1928 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Cortland County, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Delaware County, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Dutchess County, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Erie County, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Essex County, 1927-1928 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Essex County, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Franklin County, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Fulton County, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Genesee County, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Genesee County, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Greene County, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Herkimer County, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Lewis County, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Livingston County, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Madison County, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Monroe County, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Montgomery County, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Nassau County, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Niagara County, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Niagara County, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Oneida County, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Onondaga County, 1927-1928 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Onondaga County, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Onondaga County, 1927 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Ontario County, 1927 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Ontario County, 1927 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Orange County, 1927 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Orleans County, 1927 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Oswego County, 1927 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Otsego County, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Rensselaer County, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Rockland County, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Saratoga County, 1927 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Schenectady County, 1927 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Schoharie County, 1927 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Schuyler County, 1927 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Schuyler County, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Seneca County, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - St. Lawrence County, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Steuben County, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Suffolk County, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Sullivan County, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Tioga County, 1927 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Tompkins County, 1927 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Ulster County, 1927 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Ulster-Sullivan County, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Warren County, 1927 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Washington County, 1927 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Wayne County, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Westchester County, 1927 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Wyoming County, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Yates County, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 49)
- Series XII. 1928
  - Albany County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Allegany County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Broome County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Cattaraugus County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Cayuga County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Chautaugua County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Chautaugua County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Chemung County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Chenango County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Clinton County, 1928 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Columbia County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Delaware County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Dutchess County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Erie County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Erie County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Franklin County, 1928 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Fulton County, 1928 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Genesee County, 1928 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Greene County, 1928 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Herkimer County, 1928 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Jefferson County, 1928 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Jefferson County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Lewis County, 1928 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Lewis County, 1928 and 1929 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Livingston County, 1928 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Madison County, 1928 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Madison County, 1928 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Monroe County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Montgomery County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Nassau County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Niagara County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Oneida County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Onondaga County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Onondaga County, 1928 and 1929 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Ontario County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Orange County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Orleans County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Oswego County, 1928 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Otsego County, 1928 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Rensselaer County, 1928 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Rockland County, 1928 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Saratoga County, 1928 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Schenectady County, 1928 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Schenectady County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Schoharie County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Schuyler County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Seneca County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - St. Lawrence County, 1928 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Steuben County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Suffolk County, 1928 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Suffolk County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Sullivan County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Tioga County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Tompkins County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Ulster County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Warren County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Washington County, 1928 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Wayne County, 1928 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Westchester County, 1928 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Wyoming County, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Yates County, 1928 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Series XIII. 1929
  - Albany County, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Allegany County, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Broome County, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Cattaraugus County, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Cayuga County, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Cayuga County, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Chautauqua County, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Chenango County, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Clinton County, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Columbia County, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Cortland County, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Delaware County, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Dutchess County, 1929 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Erie County, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Essex County, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Franklin County, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Fulton County, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Genesee County (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Gneida County, 1929 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Greene County, 1929 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Herkimer County, 1929 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Herkimer County, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Jefferson County, 1929 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Jefferson County, 1925, 1926 and 1929 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Lewis County, 1929 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Lewis County, 1928 and 1929 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Livingston County, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Madison County, 1929 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Monroe County, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Montgomery County, 1929 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Nassau County, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Niagara County, 1929 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Oneida County, 1929 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Onondaga County, 1928 and 1929 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Orange County, 1929 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Orleans County, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Oswego County, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Oswego County, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Otsego County, 1929 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Rensselaer County, 1929 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Rockland County, 1929 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Saratoga County, 1929 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Schenectady County, 1929 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Schoharie County, 1929 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Schuyler County, 1929 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Seneca County, 1929 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - St. Lawrence County, 1929 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Steuben County, 1929 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Suffolk County, 1929 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Suffolk County, 1929 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Sullivan County, 1929 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Tioga County, 1929 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Tompkins County, 1929 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Ulster County, 1929 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Warren County, 1929 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Washington County, 1929 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Wayne County, 1929 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Westchester County, 1929 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Wyoming County, 1929 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Yates County, 1929 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Series XIV. 1930
  - Albany County, 1930 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Allegany County, 1930 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Broome County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Broome County, 1930 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Cattaraugus County, 1930 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Cayuga County, 1930 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Cayuga County, 1930 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Cayuga County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Chautaugua County, 1930 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Chautauqua County, 1930 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Chautauqua County, 1930 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Chemung County, 1930 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Clinton County, 1930 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Columbia County, 1930 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Cortland County, 1930 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Cortland County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Delaware County, 1930 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Dutchess County, 1930 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Dutchess County, 1930 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Erie County, 1930 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Erie County, 1930 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Essex County, 1930 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Franklin County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Fulton County, 1930 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Genesee County, 1930 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Genesee County, 1930 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Greene County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Herkimer County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Jefferson County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Lewis County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Livingston County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Madison County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Monroe County, 1930 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Montgomery County, 1930 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Nassau County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Niagara County, 1930 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Oneida County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Onondaga County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Onondaga County, 1930 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Onterio County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Orange County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Orange County, 1930 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Orleans County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Oswego County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Otsego County, 1930 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Rensselaer County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Saratoga County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Schenectady County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Schoharie County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Schuyler County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Seneca County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Steuben County, 1930 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Suffolk County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Sullivan County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Tioga County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Tomkins County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Ulster County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Warren County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Washington County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Wayne County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Westchester County, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Westchester County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Wyoming County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Yates County, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 40)
- Series XV. 1931
  - Albany County, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Allegany County, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Cattaraugus County, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Cayuga County, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Chautauqua County, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Chemung County, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Chenango County, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Columbia County, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Delaware County, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Delaware County, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Dutchess County, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Erie County, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Essex County, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Franklin County, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Fulton County, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Genesee County, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Greene County, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Greene County, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Herkimer County, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Jefferson County, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Lewis County, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Livingston County, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Madison County, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Monroe County, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Nassau County, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Niagara County, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Oneida County, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Onondaga County, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Ontario County, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Orange County, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Orleans County, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Oswego County, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Otsego County, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Rensselaer County, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Rockland County, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Saratoga County, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Schenectady County, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Schoharie County, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Schuyler County, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Seneca County, 1931 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - St. Lawrence County, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Steuben County, 1931 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Suffolk County, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Suffolk County, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Suffolk County, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Sullivan County, 1931 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Tioga County, 1931 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Tompkins County, 1931 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Ulster County, 1931 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Warren County, 1931 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Washington County, 1931 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Wayne County, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Wayne County, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Westchester County, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Wyoming County, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Yate County, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 42)
- Series XVI. 1932
  - Albany County, 1932 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Allegany County, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Allegany County, 1932 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Allegany, Delaware, Erie, Montgomery, and Niagara Counties, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Broome County, 1932 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Cattaraugus County, 1932 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Cayuga County, 1932 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Chautauqua County, 1932 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Chemung County, 1932 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Chenango County, 1932 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Clinton County, 1932 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Columbia County, 1932 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Cortland County, 1932 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Delaware County, 1932 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Dutchess County, 1932 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Erie County, 1932 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Essex County, 1932 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Franklin County, 1932 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Fulton County, 1932 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Genesee County, 1932 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Greene County, 1932 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Herkimer County, 1932 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Jefferson County, 1932 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Livingston County, 1932 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Madison County, 1932 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Monroe County, 1932 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Montgomery County, 1932 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Nassau County, 1932 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Niagara County, 1932 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Oneida County, 1932 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Onondaga County, 1932 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Ontario County, 1932 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Orange County, 1932 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Orleans County, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Oswego County, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Otsego County, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Rensselaer County, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Rensselaer County, 1932-1933 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Rockland County, 1932 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Rockland County, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Saratoga County, 1932 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Schenectady County, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Schoharie County, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Schuyler County, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Seneca County, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - St. Lawrence County, 1932 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - St. Lawrence County, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Steuben County, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Suffolk County, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Sullivan County, 1932 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Tioga County, 1932 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Tompkins County, 1932 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Ulster County, 1932 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Warren County, 1932 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Washington County, 1932 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Wayne County, 1932 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Wayne County, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Westchester County, 1932 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Wyoming County, 1932 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Yates County, 1932 (Box 25, Folder 33)
- Series XVII. 1933
  - Albany County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Albany County, 1933 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Allegany County, 1933 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Broome County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Cattaragus County, 1933 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Cayuga County, 1933 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Chautaugua County, 1933 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Chemung County, 1933 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Chenango County, 1933 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Clinton County, 1933 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Columbia County, 1933 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Delaware County, 1933 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Dutchess County, 1933 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Erie County, 1933 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Essex County, 1933 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Franklin County, 1933 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Fulton County, 1933 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Genesee County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Greene County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Herkimer County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Jefferson County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Lewis County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Livingston County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Madison County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Monroe County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Montgomery County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Nassau County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Niagara County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Oneida County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Onondoga County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Ontario County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Orange County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Orleans County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Oswego County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Otsego COunty, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Rensselaer County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Rockland County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Saratoga County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Schenectady County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Schoharie County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Schuyler County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Seneca County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - St. Lawrence County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Steuben County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Suffolk County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Sullivan County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Tioga County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Tompkins County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Ulster County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Warren County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Washington County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Wayne County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Westchester County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Wyoming County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Yates County, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 40)
- Series XVIII. 1934
  - Allegany County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Broome County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Cattaraugus County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Cayuga County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Chautauqua County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Chemung County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Chenango County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Clinton County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Columbia County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Delaware County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Dutchess County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Erie County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Essex County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Franklin County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Fulton County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Genesee County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Greene County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Herkimor County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Jefferson County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Livingston County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Madison County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Monroe County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Montgomery County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Nassau County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Niagara County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Oneida County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Onondaga County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Ontario County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Orange County, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Orleans County, 1934 (Box 29, Folder 2)